This is an example set of something I
would sell in the future. For this
specific set, it's going to be Fourth of
July themed. Basically, this set will
come with three different squishies and
it'll already be pre-waxed. Since this
is a pull-apart set, I do have to pour
wax on each ingredient, which can be
more costly. The reason why it would be
more expensive is because it's going to
take a lot more time to do one squishy.
I'm already 5 minutes in and I'm still
not done with the squishy because it
needs one more layer of wax so just to
make sure that it doesn't crack during
transit. I'm finally done. Now it's time
to do my second squishy. This one is
going to be the same exact routine as
the last one. Now, the hardest part
about selling these is coming up with
the price. For a three-set squishy like
this, I would have to charge $30. Some
people might agree with the price and
others might say it's too expensive. But
the reason for that price is because of
the time, product, and materials. As
many of you know, the price of wax has
gone up so much that I can't even charge
less even if I wanted to. Do you think
it's worth it? They come pre-waxed and
they sound amazing when you crack them.